tempail.com 2019-03-20

# Privacy & Policy - Free Temp Mail

_Last updated September 11, 2018_

All incoming emails and personal data temporarily stored on our service are permanently deleted after 1 hour. You can delete your temporary Email address at any time using the appropriate button “Delete” on the home page. You cannot use this Site for illegal activities.

Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Sites visit: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

**Your Personal Information**

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Sites is at your own risk. You should only access the services within a secure environment.

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Sites, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Sites. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Google AdSense™**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

**Google Analytics™**

We use Google Analytics Universal to analyse the use of our website. Our analytics service provider generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies.

The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Our analytics service provider’s privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

**The DoubleClick™**

The DoubleClick cookieis used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.

**Disqus™**

We use Disqus to let the users comment on our site’s materials and thus improve their user experience. Disqus may collect user data. You can review Disqus privacy policy is available at: <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies>. That page also contains information on how to opt out of data collection.

**Yandex Metrica™**

We also use Yandex Metrica to analyse the use of our website. Our analytics service provider’s privacy policy is available at: <https://metrica.yandex.com/about/info/privacy-policy>.

**Your Privacy Rights**

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the contact details provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm>

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: <https://tempail.com/contacts/>
